FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
Huh?
I mean... I'm one.
And I'd... say yes... if it's you
AFFECTION AND ANNOYANCE
- What do you think you're doing?!
- I don't understand...
Why did you make her cry?!
Huh?
Oh, wow... I am sorry.
No let me explain, Master's never done
anything to hurt me. He was only helping...
It's no one else's fault that I'm like
this, it's just that I... -She's uh havin' a
- hard time...
- But what happened?
F'you ask me uh' you're
better off leaving it alone.
Sadako was just complimenting you for
being friendly, cheerful and treating
- people so fairly.
- She did what?
- It's Kazehaya.
- Hey! What'cha doin... Uh?
KAZEHAYA
THE FLIRT?
SADAKO!!
- Check out the drama over here!
- What is this?
You fighting over Sadako
or something, Kazehaya?
Wow, you have two different guys trying
to win your heart! You're so popular!
W- What a cruel joke.
That's right.
What? You've gotta be kidding, you don't
actually have a crush on Sadako do you?
I do like her.
It's true... I like you... Kuronuma...
Is that a problem?
Uh, no... not really, but...
- You know?
- Yeah.
Is he being for real?
H-he's just messing with us, right?
They'll misunderstand...
They'll all end up getting the
wrong idea, if you say that.
Wait, what?
What are you trying to say? That you're
worried we'd misunderstand the two of you
might be in a relationship?
Don't worry 'bout it I'm pretty
sure we can see what's going on.
Yeah! You're worrying way too much! We
know he's just telling you he doesn't hate
- you or something like that.
- Because it'll make me want
to misunderstand those words.
What're you laughing about?
Kuronuma.
If I'm causing you
trouble, you can just say so.
Kazehaya?
Hey! Wait!
- The bell! The bell's already ringing!
- That's not good!!
We have gym!
Uh, Pin'll chew us out!
Come on, the show's
over! Let's go, let's go!
Is it just me, or did Kazehaya seem
like he was getting pretty mad at us?
I don't really know you, but why do
you have your arms on our shoulders?
Yeah, who're you again?
Kazehaya, don't tell me.
You're serious? Whaaa-?!
Aww, lunch break's over already.
- We'll have to finish after school.
- Huh? Where's Sawako? She's late.
Hm? Kazehaya isn't here yet either...
I chased after him... but I
still don't know what to do...
I can't find the words... I'm so lost.
If I'm causing you
trouble, you can just say so.
Trouble?
He has someone he likes.
Plus, you don't want to cause
trouble for him either, right?
So I was already doing that...
I didn't know he had someone he liked...
and I was trying to make him all mine.
It's true... I like you... Kuronuma...
I made him say things like that. Things
that could've easily been misunderstood by
others.
So why are you crying?
Is it because of Miura?
Master was only
comforting me to try and help.
Then... it's me?
I- I'm sorry.
You felt you had to protect my
feelings. And I caused you so much
trouble. I'm sorry.
I really am.
Protect your feelings?
So Miura's actions are kind, but if I try
to comfort or help it's causing trouble?
I was trying to be kind.
I'm not the type of guy you think I am.
The way you saw me... as someone who
was "cheerful" and "fair" to everyone...
Well I never was just...
"treating you fairly".
Because... I really like you.
Do you... like me too?
But...
My "like" and your "like"
are probably different.
Yes.
From the very beginning... I
already understood that.
He just stated the obvious...
so I guess... that's it then.
At least I thought it
was obvious... but somehow...
Let's see... Who's absent...
Kazehaya and Kuronuma?
What? Sadako?
Seriously?
Wonder where she went.
I like you.
- Kazehaya?
- Exactly! There was some serious drama
going on! You know that big flirt in Class
D? It was with the three of them.
Sadako was crying... and Kazehaya looked all
pissed off. -And when we went to check it
out he told us straight up that he
totally does like her... -Wait? Like how? He
ask her out? Huh?! Obviously not!
But according to your story at least,
doesn't it sound like he was totally
- asking her out?
- Like I said, it
clearly wasn't like that!]
I wonder if Sawako's with Kazehaya.
I hope so. Kento!
So, uh... where'd Sawako go?
Uh... -Well, I have no idea if she'd be
there anymore, but the last time I ran
into her was when we
were together outside. -Oh?
Uh-huh, it was back during lunch break,
near the bench that's by the clubhouse.
You didn't do something
you shouldn't have, did you?
Let's go. Kay?
Yeah. Anyway, thanks for that.
Uh, Hold on! Actually,
I can just go with you...
Hey, Kurumi! long time no see.
I heard there was some
drama. Kazehaya and Sawako?
Rumors travel fast.
What happened then? I need you
to tell me all of the details.
I think I might've done
something kinda uncalled-for.
So heavy...
This sucks!
I even skipped my classes...
Now, school's already over.
I have to pull myself together.
Everyone's preparing for the school
festival too. I can't be the only one
slacking off.
I don't know... should I even
let people see me like this?
Hey! What's wrong with
you?! You tryin' to kill me?!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean-
The hell are you doing, curled up
in a dark, dreary place like this?!
Uh uh- I really am sorry.
I figured you and Shota both missed
homeroom at the end of the day for a
reason. I see... Romance drama.
So how'd it go? D'you just
straight up reject the guy?
I... I got rejected.
I... was turned down.
Whaaat?!
Then... does that mean... he went through
the trouble of asking me where you were,
because he was so eager to reject you he
couldn't wait? What a complete and total
jerk. Hey, chin up!
Just forget about that
poor excuse for a man, 'kay?
- Heey!!!
- What the heck are you doing?!
That really hurt! How dare you kick
everyone's favorite homeroom teacher!
Why are you feeding her
unnecessary information!
Just get outta here!
This is bull. I was just
trying to cheer her up!
- We looked all over.
- I-I'm so sorry to trouble you.
So...
What was that just now? The
part about about being rejected.
Also... that face.
- S-Say what?!
I took my eyes off you for one
second, how did this happen?!
I'm sorry I got turned down without you.
That idiot! I was right, he really
DID do something he shouldn't have!
Hiiii!!
Sawako, That's not true.
If it's come down to
this, I'll just tell you...
I...I think I've been too full of myself.
I had always assumed... that even though
I'm like this... Kazehaya was treating me
the exact same way he treated
everyone else... but I was wrong.
It went to my head.
Well, I never was just
treating you fairly.
All along... he was just
protecting my feelings.
At the same time, the more I came to like
him, to love him, the greedier I became.
It's entirely possible...
he knew that all along...
When he told me that our idea of "like"
was different, that I misunderstood, I
think he was just trying
to tell me the obvious.
No, uh- you're
definitely misunderstanding.
I hate this.
Wait, I can understand where you're
coming from, but calm down, Chizu. -I'm
sure Kazehaya didn't mean it like that.
- Not that! I hate your attitude, Sawako.
Seriously You think we're friends with
you... because we've been worried about
- hurting your feelings or something?
- I didn't think that. I- Is that true?
Of course not... I'm saying if that's what
you think, it would seriously piss me off!
You are making Kazehaya act
this way. It's all on you! Sawako.
What do you mean, "the obvious"?
When we've been here for you too.
How much longer are you gonna be
okay with putting yourself down?
Stop acting like you're dense!
W- Wait, Chizu!
That girl...
You know how everyone avoided her and
then she got so used to it that it just
felt normal? That
really... breaks my heart.
Especially when she's so sweet.
The thing about Chizu... is that when she
gets frustrated or sad, she kinda snaps...
But she is still worried about you.
Hey, wanna know something?
At first to be totally honest we thought
you were kind of a downer... and yeah, we
saw you as an outcast too.
But that all changed. We both got to know
you. Your thoughtfulness. And that sweet
heart of yours.
And now, we've come to adore you.
I think watching you muster up the
courage and work so hard for us is what
changed our views.
And you need to realize, that in that
regard, there's no difference between you,
us or Kazehaya. But you're the
one... who needs to see it that way.
Well, I'm a little worried about Chizu,
so I'll go on ahead. Wash your face and
catch up with us.
Have I... maybe been missing
something from the start?
Chizu!
Ugh! I can't believe I did
that! I'm such an idiot! So stupid!
It's okay. Sorry, Yano-chin. You were
trying to say something back there, but I
totally cut you off.
- What were you about to say?
- Huh? Uh... Just that the person
Kazehaya likes is actually Sawako."
I figured if it's this
messy, I might as well tell her.
Yeah! Well, that would have
solved everything, so why didn't you?!
Huh?
Still in the end, I thought that
everything you said to her was really spot
on. Her perspective is skewed and
that just tangles everything all up.
Besides...
I'm sure Sawako will do something about
it all by herself. She's done that with
everything else up until now.
It's gonna work out. I'm sure!
Yeah, you're right.
I think watching you muster up the
courage and work so hard for us is what
changed our views.
Back then...
I was definitely putting in effort.
But when I think about it... have I actually
put in that same kind of effort... when it
comes to Kazehaya?
And now?
Can I honestly say... that
right now... I'm giving it my all?]
Dense, timid, lacking in words.
Next time: "Just Give Up"